const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Vanya is going to visit his friend this week.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who is going to visit his friend?",2:"What is going to visit his friend?",3:"Who is Vanya going?",4:"When is going to visit his friend Vanya?"}},{type:"test",question:"Who is there?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"We are",2:"We is",3:"We am",4:"They is"}},{type:"test",question:"Masha speaks English perfectly.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who speaks English perfectly?",2:"Who does speak English perfectly?",3:"Who Masha speaks English?",4:"How does speak English Masha?"}},{type:"test",question:"She wrote some messages to our colleges in Russia.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who wrote some messages?",2:"Who she did write messages?",3:"Our colleges wrote messages?",4:"Who did write messages?"}},{type:"test",question:"The presents are over there.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What is over there?",2:"What are over there?",3:"What presents over there?",4:"Presents over there?"}},{type:"test",question:"Something strange has happened in the college.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What has happened in the college?",2:"What strange has happened in the college?",3:"Who did happened?",4:"Who did happen in the college?"}},{type:"test",question:"Vanya was cooking dinner when the phone rang.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who was cooking dinner when the phone rang?",2:"What did the phone do?",3:"What was cooking Vanya when the phone rang?",4:"Who did the phone ring?"}},{type:"test",question:"Who is your friend?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Masha is.",2:"Masha was.",3:"Masha has.",4:"Masha."}},{type:"test",question:"Mary is going to have the vegetable salad.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who is going to have the vegetable salad?",2:"Who Mary is going to do?",3:"What is going to have Mary?",4:"What Mary is going to have?"}},{type:"test",question:"Natasha loves cakes.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who loves cakes?",2:"What loves Natasha?",3:"What Natasha is?",4:"When loves cakes?"}}]},{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Кто был в библиотеке, когда ты пришел?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who was in the library when you came?",2:"Who came to the library when you were there?",3:"What was in the library when you were coming?",4:"What were you doing in the library when somebody came?"}},{type:"test",question:"Что помогло тебе довести дело до конца?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What helped you to finish the matter?",2:"What did help you to finish the matter?",3:"Who helped you?",4:"Who did helped you to finish the matter?"}},{type:"test",question:"Что может помочь тебе поверить в себя?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What can help you to believe in yourself?",2:"What did can help you to believe in yourself?",3:"What can did help you to believe in yourself?",4:"Why to believe in yourself?"}},{type:"test",question:"Кто твой самый лучший друг?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who is your best friend?",2:"What is your best friend?",3:"What your best friend is?",4:"Who your best friend?"}},{type:"test",question:"Кто съел всю мою еду?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who did eat all my food?",2:"Who ate all my food?",3:"What ate all my food?",4:"What did eat all my food?"}}]}]};export{e as default};
